export const Decks = {
    hiragana: [
        {question: 'What does "あ" mean?', answer: "A"},
        {question: 'What does "い" mean?', answer: "I"},
        {question: 'What does "う" mean?', answer: "U"},
        {question: 'What does "え" mean?', answer: "E"},
        {question: 'What does "お" mean?', answer: "O"},
        {question: 'What does "か" mean?', answer: "KA"},
        {question: 'What does "き" mean?', answer: "KI"},
        {question: 'What does "く" mean?', answer: "KU"},
        {question: 'What does "け" mean?', answer: "KE"},
        {question: 'What does "こ" mean?', answer: "KO"},
        {question: 'What does "さ" mean?', answer: "SA"},
        {question: 'What does "し" mean?', answer: "SHI"},
        {question: 'What does "す" mean?', answer: "SU"},
        {question: 'What does "せ" mean?', answer: "SE"},
        {question: 'What does "そ" mean?', answer: "SO"},
        {question: 'What does "た" mean?', answer: "TA"},
        {question: 'What does "ち" mean?', answer: "CHI"},
        {question: 'What does "つ" mean?', answer: "TSU"},
        {question: 'What does "て" mean?', answer: "TE"},
        {question: 'What does "と" mean?', answer: "TO"},
        {question: 'What does "な" mean?', answer: "NA"},
        {question: 'What does "に" mean?', answer: "NI"},
        {question: 'What does "ぬ" mean?', answer: "NU"},
        {question: 'What does "ね" mean?', answer: "NE"},
        {question: 'What does "の" mean?', answer: "NO"},
        {question: 'What does "は" mean?', answer: "HA"},
        {question: 'What does "ひ" mean?', answer: "HI"},
        {question: 'What does "ふ" mean?', answer: "FU"},
        {question: 'What does "へ" mean?', answer: "HE"},
        {question: 'What does "ほ" mean?', answer: "HO"},
        {question: 'What does "ま" mean?', answer: "MA"},
        {question: 'What does "み" mean?', answer: "MI"},
        {question: 'What does "む" mean?', answer: "MU"},
        {question: 'What does "め" mean?', answer: "ME"},
        {question: 'What does "も" mean?', answer: "MO"},
        {question: 'What does "や" mean?', answer: "YA"},
        {question: 'What does "ゆ" mean?', answer: "YU"},
        {question: 'What does "よ" mean?', answer: "YO"},
        {question: 'What does "ら" mean?', answer: "RA"},
        {question: 'What does "り" mean?', answer: "RI"},
        {question: 'What does "る" mean?', answer: "RU"},
        {question: 'What does "れ" mean?', answer: "RE"},
        {question: 'What does "ろ" mean?', answer: "RO"},
        {question: 'What does "わ" mean?', answer: "WA"},
        {question: 'What does "を" mean?', answer: "WO"},
        {question: 'What does "ん" mean?', answer: "N"}
    ], 

    katakana: [
        {question: 'What does "ア" mean?', answer: "A"},
        {question: 'What does "イ" mean?', answer: "I"},
        {question: 'What does "ウ" mean?', answer: "U"},
        {question: 'What does "エ" mean?', answer: "E"},
        {question: 'What does "オ" mean?', answer: "O"},
        {question: 'What does "カ" mean?', answer: "KA"},
        {question: 'What does "キ" mean?', answer: "KI"},
        {question: 'What does "ク" mean?', answer: "KU"},
        {question: 'What does "ケ" mean?', answer: "KE"},
        {question: 'What does "コ" mean?', answer: "KO"},
        {question: 'What does "サ" mean?', answer: "SA"},
        {question: 'What does "シ" mean?', answer: "SHI"},
        {question: 'What does "ス" mean?', answer: "SU"},
        {question: 'What does "セ" mean?', answer: "SE"},
        {question: 'What does "ソ" mean?', answer: "SO"},
        {question: 'What does "タ" mean?', answer: "TA"},
        {question: 'What does "チ" mean?', answer: "CHI"},
        {question: 'What does "ツ" mean?', answer: "TSU"},
        {question: 'What does "テ" mean?', answer: "TE"},
        {question: 'What does "ト" mean?', answer: "TO"},
        {question: 'What does "ナ" mean?', answer: "NA"},
        {question: 'What does "ニ" mean?', answer: "NI"},
        {question: 'What does "ヌ" mean?', answer: "NU"},
        {question: 'What does "ネ" mean?', answer: "NE"},
        {question: 'What does "ノ" mean?', answer: "NO"},
        {question: 'What does "ハ" mean?', answer: "HA"},
        {question: 'What does "ヒ" mean?', answer: "HI"},
        {question: 'What does "フ" mean?', answer: "FU"},
        {question: 'What does "ヘ" mean?', answer: "HE"},
        {question: 'What does "ホ" mean?', answer: "HO"},
        {question: 'What does "マ" mean?', answer: "MA"},
        {question: 'What does "ミ" mean?', answer: "MI"},
        {question: 'What does "ム" mean?', answer: "MU"},
        {question: 'What does "メ" mean?', answer: "ME"},
        {question: 'What does "モ" mean?', answer: "MO"},
        {question: 'What does "ヤ" mean?', answer: "YA"},
        {question: 'What does "ユ" mean?', answer: "YU"},
        {question: 'What does "ヨ" mean?', answer: "YO"},
        {question: 'What does "ラ" mean?', answer: "RA"},
        {question: 'What does "リ" mean?', answer: "RI"},
        {question: 'What does "ル" mean?', answer: "RU"},
        {question: 'What does "レ" mean?', answer: "RE"},
        {question: 'What does "ロ" mean?', answer: "RO"},
        {question: 'What does "ワ" mean?', answer: "WA"},
        {question: 'What does "ヲ" mean?', answer: "WO"},
        {question: 'What does "ン" mean?', answer: "N"}
    ]
}   
